# Jeet Jitendra Shah

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeet-shah-45a31b16a/ | jjshah2410@gmail.com | 9870601020

#### :Objective

A graduate professional with exceptional communication and interpersonal skills, which help to build sustainable and positive relations with the stakeholders across profit and non-profit organizations. I hold industry experience of more than 11 years in client relationship management, customer success operations management, program management, talent acquisition, market research and other roles.

#### Professional experience

## Operations Manager - Student Success, WhiteHat Jr., Mumbai (Sep 2020 - Present)

- .Mentored and monitored a team of 7 members to increase productivity and efficiency in the team
- Identified business development opportunities with a key focus on growing business with existing clients and implemented ideas for marketing initiatives and sales promotion to acquire new clients
- Maintained, analyzed and identified trends from a database of 15,000+ students and coordinated with relevant teams and stakeholders to execute the same
- Built music program from 0 to 1 in less than 6 months time, making it a successful program with a renewal percentage of 26.7%
- Ensured successful ticket resolution within a TAT of 24 hours by coordinating with the customer success team; ensuring quick turnaround of fulfillment of student rewards.
- Manage day to day operations for a smooth academic delivery consisting of project feedback, doubt resolution, live sessions, mentoring and vendor management. Deliver projects and products within budget, timeline, and resource constraints.
- Create and sustain a network of professional freelancers and industry experts for grading, mentorship, which helps to maintain and monitor quality, project plans, project schedules, budgets and expenditures.
- Work with the Technology team to automate dashboards, analyze and interpret data. Apply knowledge and experience along with the analytical approach to diagnose and resolve issues in unique and complex customer environments.
- Created weekly reports and modified operational processes to improve efficiency.

#### Relationship Manager, Whitehat Jr., Mumbai (June 2020 - Sep 2020)

- Managed more than 500 Accounts on Monthly Basis, with a CSAT score of 96%, and Quality score of 99%
- .Handled esteemed VVIP clients and Brand Ambassadors of the company
- Assisted the senior team to create templates, scripts and SOP for process automation

#### Researcher, Whitecrow Research, Mumbai (Aug 2019 - May 2020)

- Worked with 50+ clients across the globe for initiatives involving recruitment for Mid , Senior and Director-level recruitment
- Sourced, screened, shortlisted 2400 resumes through job portals like Naukri, Angelist, Hirist, Linkedin, .Social Media platforms, Networking events and through references
- Conducted 2200 telephonic interviews to evaluate candidates for interpersonal communication, professionalism in a span of 11 months
- Successfully placed 4 C-suite, 9 Directors and President, and 60+ Mid/ Senior level recruits for leading .companies across 15 countries

#### Customer Service Representative, Barclays, Mumbai (Dec 2016 – Mar 2019)

- .Achieved NPS score of 96% on a weekly basis with AHT less than 3 mins
- Managed key accounts of more than 500 Account Managers for more than 50,000 customers to minimize financial risk and fraudulent activities
- Oversee Sales and Business development opportunities for promoting new products to clients

#### Customer relationship Associate, Serco Global, Mumbai (Feb 2015 -Dec 2016)

- Influencing customers to buy or retain product or service with a retention of 40% of existing clients
- Client service management, process management and maintaining client relationships, which resulted in an .increase in sales by 5%

- Generated leads for business teams to get more than 5 small or large scale businesses registered on a daily
  .basis
- .Managed 100+ customer complaints and closed it with more than 95% customer satisfaction

#### Event Promoter/Anchor/Event Coordinator, Paramount Events (Mar 2011 - Oct 2011)

- Organized and managed 35 events for various companies, like Google, Samsung, HTC, Pediasure, Marlboro, .Classic, Kooh games, Mixed bag events, paramount events, etc
- Maintained client relations and generated 15+ leads on a weekly basis by promoting the brands

### **Educational Qualifications**

Bachelors in Commerce - Solapur University - 2014 - Grade A Higher Secondary School - Maharashtra Board - 2011 - Grade A

### Skills

- Team Building
- Operations Management
- Project & Program Management
- Stakeholder Management
- Strategic planning
- Artificial Intelligence learning tools
- Client Relations Management
- Customer Success Initiatives
- Quick Learning & Processing abilities

### Certification s

- Microsoft office using AI tools by Be10x
- Project Management Certification by LearnTube